Guide to the Chelsea Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Chelsea records
1967-2013
1990-2013
GEN MSS 1090
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
49.65
(74 boxes) + 1 art
Chelsea Associates
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Alfredo de Palchi, 2002-2013.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Boxes 6, 21-22, 27, 33-34, 38-39, 42, 44-45, 52, 56, 60, 63, 65, 68, 72, and 74 (digital media): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Boxes 23, 28, and 53 (audiovisual media): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Chelsea
Semi-annual literary journal published in New York City, 1958-2007. Founded in 1958 by Ursule Molinaro, George Economou, Venable Herndon, and Robert and Joan Kelly, the journal was originally titled Chelsea Review; the title was changed to Chelsea in 1960. Chelsea was published by Chelsea Associates and edited by Sona Raiziss and Alfredo de Palchi, 1966-1994, and after Raiziss's death in 1994, by de Palchi, 1995-2007. The journal administered the Chelsea Award for Poetry and the Chelsea Award for Short Fiction.
Alfredo de Palchi (1926-)
Italian poet and translator. De Palchi was born in Italy and emigrated to the United States, settling in New York City in 1956. In 1952 he married poet and translator Sona Raiziss, with whom he edited the the literary journal Chelsea, 1966-1994. After Raiziss's death in 1994, de Palchi edited Chelsea, 1994-2007, and has continued to manage the Sonia Raiziss Giop Charitable Foundation. He married Rita di Pace in 1989. Chelsea Editions, a subdivision of Chelsea Associates, edited by de Palchi, publishes bilingual editions of literature, mostly contemporary Italian poetry with English translation.
Sona Raiziss (1909-1994)
American poet and translator, also spelled Sonia Raiziss. Raiziss was born in Germany, was raised in Philadelphia, and attended the University of Pennsylvania, Cornell University, and Columbia University. Her translations include poetry of Alfredo de Palchi, whom she married in 1952. With de Palchi, she edited the the literary journal Chelsea, 1966-1994. Raiziss founded the Sonia Raiziss Giop Charitable Foundation, which continues to fund the Jane Austen Essay Contest, the Bordighera Poetry Prize, and the Raiziss/de Palchi Translation Awards.
Scope and Contents
Manuscripts by authors, translators, and artists, submitted to Chelsea during editorship of Sona Raiziss and Alfredo de Palchi, encompassing issues 20/21 (1966)-82/83 (2007), with related author contracts, photographs, issue drafts and proofs, and digital files; similar materials for books published by Chelsea Editions, 1990s-2010s; Chelsea editorial meeting minutes and other administrative files, including digital files; correspondence between Chelsea contributors and Raiziss, de Palchi, and associate editors and guest editors including Andrea Lockett, Richard Foerester, Brian Swann, and Gerard Malanga, with additional writings and digital email files, 1960s-2010s; applications and manuscripts, including digital files, submitted by authors for the Raiziss/de Palchi Translation Awards, administered by the Academy of American Poets, and other literary prizes, 2000s; writings by Raiziss and de Palchi; printed material about poetry events and art exhibits; a few audiocassettes of literary readings by Raiziss; and a few award plaques and t-shirts relating to literary organizations. Research strengths include the history of Chelsea; little magazine and small press publishing in the United States, 1960s-2010s; and literary prizes, especially the Chelsea Award for Poetry, the Chelsea Award for Short Fiction, and the Raiziss/de Palchi Translation Awards.
Related Materials
Associated material: Alfredo de Palchi and Sona Raiziss papers (GEN MSS 947), Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library.
Books owned by de Palchi or Raiziss may be found in the online catalog by searching "de Palchi, Alfredo" or "Raiziss, Sona" as a special collections subject.
Arrangement
Organized into sixteen groupings: January 2002 Acquisition, September 2004 Acquisition, April 2005 Acquisition, November 2005 Acquisition, April 2006 Acquisition, August 2006 Acquisition, June 2007 Acquisition, November 2007 Acquisition, April 2008 Acquisition, September 2008 Acquisition, April 2009 Acquisition, November 2009 Acquisition, August 2010 Acquisition, January 2011 Acquisition, November 2012 Acquisition, and May 2013 Acquisition.
Chelsea (New York, N.Y.); American poetry -- 20th Century; American poetry -- 21st century; Authors, American -- 20th Century; Authors, American -- 21st century; Authors, Italian -- 20th Century; Authors, Italian -- 21st century; Italian poetry -- 20th Century -- Translations into English; Italian poetry -- 21st century -- Translations into English; Literary prizes -- United States; Literary prizes -- Italy; Little magazines -- United States; Poets, American -- 20th Century; Poets, American -- 21st century; Poets, Italian -- 20th Century; Poets, Italian -- 21st century; Women poets, American -- 20th Century; Women poets, American -- 21st century; Audiovisual materials -- United States -- 20th Century; Born digital -- United States -- 20th Century; Photographs -- United States -- 20th Century; Plaques (flat objects) -- Italy -- 20th Century; Sound recordings -- United States -- 20th Century; De Palchi, Alfredo, 1926-; De Palchi, Alfredo, 1926- -- Translations into English; Foerester, Richard; Lockett, Andrea; Malanga, Gerard, 1943-; Raiziss, Sona; Swann, Brian, 1940-; Academy of American Poets; Chelsea Associates; Chelsea Editions
- January 2002 Acquisition, 1958-2001; 14.25; (16 boxes)
  - Correspondence
    - Ackerman, Diane, 1974-1976 (Box 1)
    - Adams, Barbara, 1972-1977 (Box 1)
    - Adams, Betsy, 1983, undated (Box 1)
    - Agron, Michael, 1960 (Box 1)
    - Aldan, Daisy, 1961-1971 (Box 1)
    - Alegria, Fernando, 1960 (Box 1)
    - Alwan, Ameen, 1973-1975 (Box 1)
    - Ammons, A. R., 1962-1965, undated (Box 1)
    - Amou, Ben, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Anderson, Jack, 1968 September 5 (Box 1)
    - Andrews, Bruce, 1971, undated (Box 1)
    - Antin, David, 1964, undated (Box 1)
    - Appleman, Philip, 1970-1975 (Box 1)
    - Ardery, Peter B., 1966-1968 (Box 1)
    - Awoonor, Kofi, 1970 (Box 1)
    - Balaban, John, 1968-1975 (Box 1)
    - Balakian, Anna, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Barks, Coleman, 1965-1969 (Box 1)
    - Bees, Julian, 1965-1966, undated (Box 1)
    - Benedikt, Michael, 1966-1980 (Box 1)
    - Bennani, Benjamin, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Bergé, Carol, 1970-1972 (Box 1)
    - Bergin, Thomas Goddard, 1960-1965, undated (Box 1)
    - Berman, Cassia, 1971 January 20 (Box 1)
    - Bernstein, Charles, 1976 October 26 (Box 1)
    - Berry, Wendell, 1969 June 3 (Box 1)
    - Birney, Earle, 1961-1966 (Box 1)
    - Blazek, Douglas, undated (Box 1)
    - Bly, Robert, 1959-1972 (Box 1)
    - Bock, Frederick, 1963-1977 (Box 1)
    - Bonazzi, Robert, 1972-1974, undated (Box 1)
    - Bortolotto, Mario, 1964 (Box 1)
    - Bradley, Sam, 1959-1972 (Box 1)
    - Brand, Millen, 1967-1982 (Box 1)
    - Braun, Henry, 1961 (Box 1)
    - Brown, Spencer, 1963-1965 (Box 1)
    - Brunauer, Dalma Hunyadi, 1973 May 2 (Box 1)
    - Buck, Ashley, 1974-1978, undated (Box 1)
    - Burns, Robert Grant, 1964-1971 (Box 1)
    - Campbell, Katherine, 1964-1965 (Box 1)
    - Carruth, Hayden, 1960 (Box 1)
    - Carver, Raymond, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Casto, Robert Clayton, 1959-1964 (Box 1)
    - Cedering, Siv, 1974-1975 (Box 1)
    - Chabrowe, Leonard, 1973-1974 (Box 1)
    - Chatterji, N., 1967-1968 (Box 1)
    - Chickering, Howell D., 1964-1965 (Box 1)
    - Ciardi, John, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Claire, William F., 1974 (Box 1)
    - Clark, Alan, 1972-1979 (Box 1)
    - Coles, Robert, 1967-1969 (Box 1)
    - Collins, Jess, 1960 (Box 1)
    - Colt, Byron, 1960-1961 (Box 1)
    - Conroy, Jack, 1960-1974 (Box 1)
    - Contoski, Victor, 1967-1976 (Box 1)
    - Cook, Albert, 1960-1974 (Box 1)
    - Cook, Margaret W., 1972, undated (Box 1)
    - Cordier, Robert, 1962-1963 (Box 1)
    - Corrington, John William, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Crawford, Jack, 1964-1968 (Box 1)
    - Davis, Christopher, 1965 (Box 1)
    - Davis, Ossie, 1968 February 19 (Box 1)
    - Dawson, Fielding, 1972 (Box 1)
    - Denney, Reuel, 1960 (Box 1)
    - Di Emilio, Monica, 1970, undated (Box 1)
    - Di Giovanni, Norman Thomas, 1963-1965 (Box 1)
    - Dobell, Edith, 1959, undated (Box 1)
    - Dobrin, Arthur, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
    - Dowden, George, 1962-1964 (Box 1)
    - Drabkin, David L. (David Lion), 1967 June 23 (Box 1)
    - Duffy, James, 1959-1960 (Box 1)
    - Dunford, Nelson, 1962-1967 (Box 1)
    - Dworzan, Hélène, 1971, undated (Box 1)
    - Dybek, Stuart, 1975-1981 (Box 1)
    - Eaton, Charles Edward, 1960-1985 (Box 1)
    - Eberhart, Richard, 1959-1967 (Box 1)
    - Eckman, Frederick, 1960-1961 (Box 1)
    - Ecommore, George, 1970-1972 (Box 1)
    - Edkins, Anthony, 1970-1975 (Box 1)
    - Elevitch, M. D. (Morton D.), 1972-1989, undated (Box 1)
    - Errante, Guido, 1959-1960 (Box 1)
    - Eshleman, Clayton, 1960-1961 (Box 1)
    - Farber, Charles, 1960-1962 (Box 1)
    - Feldman, Morton, 1964 (Box 1)
    - Feldman, Ruth, 1973-1980 (Box 1)
    - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence, 1976, undated (Box 1)
    - Fernandez, Benedict J., 1968 June 17 (Box 1)
    - Fink, Jon Stephen, 1975, undated (Box 1)
    - Finkel, Donald, 1961-1964 (Box 1)
    - Fitzgerald, Robert, 1964-1965 (Box 1)
    - Fjelde, Rolf, 1959-1960 (Box 1)
    - Foerster, Richard, 1986-1998 (Box 1)
    - Foulke, Adrienne W., 1965-1966 (Box 1)
    - Fox, Hugh, undated (Box 1)
    - Frankenberg, Lloyd, 1960 (Box 1)
    - Hejduk, John, 1982, undated (Box 1)
    - Honecker, George, 1981, undated (Box 1)
    - Ignatow, David, 1971-1990 (Box 1)
    - Ignatow, Rose Graubart, 1970-1991, undated; 7 (Box 1)
    - Jacobs, Mark, 1971-1978 (Box 2)
    - Johnson Reprint Corporation, 1964-1969 (Box 2)
    - Kirkham, Michael, 1970-1978, undated; 2 (Box 2)
    - Lanza, Francesco, 1964, undated (Box 2)
    - MacShane, Frank, 1972, undated (Box 2)
    - The Magazine Co-op, 1975-1977, undated (Box 2)
    - Poetry Society of America; PEN; Poets & Writers, Inc.; and Poets House, 1975-1986, undated; 2 (Box 2)
    - Pushcart Press, 1969-2000, undated; 2 (Box 2)
    - Sharat Chandra, G. S., 1972-1973 (Box 2)
    - Swann, Brian, 1973-1993, undated; 8 (Box 2)
    - University of Texas at Dallas. Center for Translation Studies, 1977-1983 (Box 2)
    - Wisniewski, Mark S., 1997-1999, undated (Box 2)
    - Zittou, Herbert, 1980-1983, undated (Box 2)
    - About "assistant editor advertisement", 1976-1993, undated; 4 (Box 2)
    - About "Laura (Riding) Jackson tribute, 1992", 3 (Box 2)
    - "Comic correspondence", 1965-2000, undated (Box 2)
    - "Loony letters", 1961-1980, undated; 4 (Box 2)
    - "Prisoners", 1975-1995 (Box 2)
    - Unsorted, 1959-2000, undated; 33 (Box 3)
    - Unsorted, 1958-2000, undated; 37 (Box 4)
    - Unsorted, 1958-2000, undated; 15 (Box 5)
  - Chelsea Issues
    - Chelsea 20/21 (1967), 2 (Box 5)
    - Chelsea 26 (1969), 2 (Box 5)
    - Chelsea 27 (1969) (Box 5)
    - Chelsea 28 (1970) (Box 5)
    - Chelsea 29 (1971), 2 (Box 5)
    - Chelsea 30/31 (1972) (Box 5)
    - Chelsea 32 (1973), 3 (Box 5)
    - Chelsea 33 (1974), 4 (Box 5)
    - Chelsea 34 (1975), 3 (Box 6)
    - Chelsea 35 (1976) (Box 6)
    - Chelsea 35 (1976) (Box 15 (Oversize))
    - Chelsea 36 (1977), 4 (Box 6)
    - Chelsea 37 (1978), 2 (Box 6)
    - Chelsea 40 (1981), 2 (Box 6)
    - Chelsea 41 (1982) (Box 6)
    - Chelsea 42/43 (1984). Introduction by Sona Raiziss, 3 (Box 6)
    - Chelsea 44 (1985), 3 (Box 6)
    - Chelsea 45 (1986), 2 (Box 6)
    - Chelsea 46 (1987), 7 (Box 6)
    - Chelsea 46 (1987), 2 (Box 7)
    - Chelsea 50 (1991), 2 (Box 7)
    - Chelsea 51 (1991) (Box 7)
    - Chelsea 52 (1992), 5 (Box 7)
    - Chelsea 53 (1992), 2 (Box 7)
    - Chelsea 54 (1993), 2 (Box 7)
    - Chelsea 55 (1993), 5 (Box 7)
    - Chelsea 56 (1994), 10 (Box 7)
    - Chelsea 57 (1994), 4 (Box 7)
    - Chelsea 57 (1994), 3 (Box 8)
    - Chelsea 58 (1995), 9 (Box 8)
    - Chelsea 59 (1995), 9 (Box 8)
    - Chelsea 60 (1996), 17 (Box 8)
    - Chelsea 61 (1996), 16 (Box 9)
    - Chelsea 62 (1997), 12 (Box 9)
    - Chelsea 62 (1997) (Box 15 (Oversize))
    - Chelsea 63 (1997), 7 (Box 9)
    - Chelsea 63 (1997), 10 (Box 10)
    - Chelsea 64 (1998), 14 (Box 10)
    - Chelsea 64 (1998) (Box 15 (Oversize))
    - Chelsea 65 (1998), 12 (Box 10)
    - Chelsea 65 (1998), 2 (Box 11)
    - Chelsea 66 (1999), 10 (Box 11)
    - Chelsea 67 (1999), 15 (Box 11)
    - Chelsea 68 (2000), 8 (Box 11)
    - Chelsea 68 (2000), 4 (Box 12)
    - Chelsea 69 (2000), 18 (Box 12)
    - Chelsea 70/71 (2001), 14 (Box 12)
    - Chelsea 70/71 (2001), 16 folders, including 2 zip disks (Box 13)
    - Chelsea (unidentified issues), undated; 4 (Box 13)
  - Other Writings
    - Ashton, Dore. "Roundtrip", undated (Box 13)
    - Freud, Esti D. Vignettes Of My Life, 1979 November (Box 13)
    - Malanga, Gerard. 3 Poems For Benedetta Barzini, 1967 (Box 15 (Oversize))
    - Phillips, Robert. "Looking For Joy: Memories of John Logan", undated (Box 13)
    - Phillips, Robert. "Remembering John Logan", undated (Box 13)
    - Reynolds, Tim. Two Poems, 1967 (Box 13)
    - Roskolenko, Harry. "New Years & Old Years, 1960-1978", 1977 (Box 13)
    - Spanos, William V. "A Biographical and Critical Note on Yannis Ritsos", undated (Box 13)
    - Unidentified, undated; 8 (Box 13)
  - Other Papers
    - "Exchange Ads with other Magazines", 1973-1991, undated; 2 (Box 13)
    - Editorial meetings minutes, 1996-1999, undated (Box 13)
    - Reviews of Chelsea, 1958-1986, undated; 4 (Box 14)
    - Photographs, 1965, undated (Box 14)
    - Contributor biographies, 1963-1973, undated; 5 (Box 14)
    - Mailing lists for Chelsea 56-68, undated; 6 (Box 14)
  - Restricted Fragile Material
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted fragile material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Computer media, 2 zip disks
      - Chelsea 70/71 corrections 9.18.01 Job # 149547, 2002-ycal-0103-u-0001; 1 (Box 16)
        Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Chelsea 70/71 2 covers + TIFF file + fonts 149547, 2002-ycal-0103-u-0002; 1 (Box 16)
- September 2004 Acquisition, 1937-2003; 4.8; (7 boxes)
  - Correspondence
    - Unsorted, 2003-2004, undated; 21 (Box 17)
  - Chelsea Issues
    - Chelsea 72 (2002), 3 (Box 18)
    - Chelsea 73 (2002), 12 folders, including 29 3.5 inch disks and 1 zip disk (Box 18)
    - Chelsea 74 (2003), 9 (Box 18)
    - Chelsea 74 (2003), 10 folders, including 26 3.5 inch disks and 1 CD (Box 19)
    - Chelsea 75 (2003), 15 (Box 19)
    - Chelsea 75 (2003) (Box 20)
    - Chelsea 72 (2002), 12 folders, including 27 3.5 inch disks, 2 zip disks, and 1 CD (Box 17)
  - Other Writings
    - Galante, Carlo. Essenza carnale (setting of poems by Alfredo de Palchi for jazz ensemble and speaker) (sound recording), 2003; 1 CD
    - Raiziss, Sona. Annotated list of literary magazines, undated (Box 20)
    - Raiziss, Sona. "Books and Authors to be Read" (notebook), 1937; 2 (Box 20)
    - Raiziss, Sona. "Books and Authors to be Read" (materials formerly laid in notebook), 1937 (Box 20)
    - Weidner, Lise. Creator of Living Poetry (with sound recording), undated; 1 folder, including 1 CD (Box 20)
  - Other Papers
    - Printed material, 2002-2003 (Box 20)
  - Computer media and Audiovisual materials
    - Computer media, 82 3.5 inch disks, 3 Zip disks, 2 CDs
      - "FOOTNOTE" by Romulus Linney in Word Perfect 6.0 (WP 6.0) Call up! FOOTNOT Chelsea 72, 2004-genm-0923-d-0001; 1 (Box 21)
      - "Avrile," D.E. Steward for Spring 2002 issue MAC Word 18iv02 D.E. Steward Box 1239 Princeton, NJ 08542-1239 desteward@workmail.com, 2004-genm-0923-d-0002; 1 (Box 21)
      - Caproni translated by Condini Lament/Lamento Leaves/Foglic Three Improvisations/ Tre Improvvisi, 2004-genm-0923-d-0003; 1 (Box 21)
      - Karen Kovacik "Going to Lvov" Chelsea Award for Short Fiction, 2004-genm-0923-d-0004; 1 (Box 21)
      - RED RIGHT RETURNING - RTF + TANGO -RTF (Chelsea 72) SUSAN E. SCHIFF 550 MADISON WAY PALO ALTO, CA 94303 (650) 321-9979, 2004-genm-0923-d-0005; 1 (Box 21)
      - RED RIGHT RETURNING - RTF + TANGO -RTF (Chelsea 72) SUSAN E. SCHIFF 550 MADISON WAY PALO ALTO, CA 94303 (650) 321-9979, 2004-genm-0923-d-0006; 1 (Box 21)
      - Kathleen McGookey WordPerfect 5.1 a:\omaha a:\success a:\notes a:\accident, 2004-genm-0923-d-0007; 1 (Box 21)
      - A Note on Alberto Savinio Blake Robinson - translator "At Auction_Life" for "Chelsea" 72, 2004-genm-0923-d-0008; 1 (Box 21)
      - Cynthia Atkins "What to Do When Your Dog Leaves You" "The Information Age") (2 poems), 2004-genm-0923-d-0009; 1 (Box 21)
      - Kira Henehan-- "Riding to Quiet" (Rich Text Format) Chelsea 72 (fiction), 2004-genm-0923-d-0010; 1 (Box 21)
      - Woodard/Leporace Amelia Rosselli Translations Rich Text Format from PC Microsoft Word 97, 2004-genm-0923-d-0011; 1 (Box 21)
      - Greg Pendergast 7297 Jackson Ave. Apt. G Mechanicsville, VA 23111 Chelsea Award for Poetry, 2004-genm-0923-d-0012; 1 (Box 21)
      - Peter LaSalle Story "Afterwards" (Corrected) for Chelsea Word 98 MAC Formatted, 2004-genm-0923-d-0013; 1 (Box 21)
      - Rachel Cantor "Rose No One" Chelsea 72, 2004-genm-0923-d-0014; 1 (Box 21)
      - The Source of my Blue Kyoshida, 2004-genm-0923-d-0015; 1 (Box 21)
      - Michael David Roberts "Withdrawl" "Passages" "Vacation in Paradise" "The Gravity of Water" Rich Text Format, 2004-genm-0923-d-0016; 1 (Box 21)
      - Poems: "The Physics of Graveyards" "Light" Also: Bio Kevin Dobbs, 2004-genm-0923-d-0017; 1 (Box 21)
      - Poems for Chelsea 72 (7 poems) Barbara Carle Microsoft Word FOR MAC, 2004-genm-0923-d-0018; 1 (Box 21)
      - for CHELSEA 72 3 poems by Silvio Giussani translated by Gayle Ridinger, 2004-genm-0923-d-0019; 1 (Box 21)
      - Chelsea 72 Meg Waite Clayton "Names You Wouldn't Think You Could Forget" Formatted in Appleworks 6 for Macintosh, 2004-genm-0923-d-0020; 1 (Box 21)
      - Chelsea 72/Bob Varel Petoskey, Mich poems: Because Nothing Is (becausen.rtf Coming Over the Dune...(ovrdune.rtf) The Widows (widows.rtf), 2004-genm-0923-d-0021; 1 (Box 21)
      - Reviews by Michael Dumanis and Amber Dermont Poem by Michael Dumanis Contributors' Notes for Michael Dumanis and Amber Dermont, 2004-genm-0923-d-0022; 1 (Box 21)
      - Review of Sheehan and McQuade by Jerry Harp Chelsea 72, 2004-genm-0923-d-0023; 1 (Box 21)
      - Alex Heminway reviews of Claire Mahoux + Venus Khoury-Ghata te by Marilyn Hacker (Chelsea 72), 2004-genm-0923-d-0024; 1 (Box 21)
      - Ramat NED CONDINI 8 Meadow Lane Montvale, NJ 07645 USA Chelsea 72 Review of Sharing a Trip, 2004-genm-0923-d-0025; 1 (Box 21)
      - On Gradiva Publications for Chelsea 72 Barbara Carle, 2004-genm-0923-d-0026; 1 (Box 21)
      - JOSHUA Kryah -"WESTERN" -"HORSE" -"HOTEL CINCO DE MAYO" -"HUM AND HAW" -BIO Chelsea 72, 2004-genm-0923-d-0030; 1 (Box 21)
      - Chelsea 72 Eugene Guillevic 6 poems translated by Patrick Moran, 2004-genm-0923-d-0027; 1 (Box 22)
      - Julie Suk - poems, 2004-genm-0923-d-0028; 1 (Box 22)
      - "Barbed Wire" c. Brooks Walker 2002 All Rights Reserved brookswalkerphoto@yahoo.com, 2004-genm-0923-d-0029; 1 (Box 22)
      - Kyle Thompson "Novena Of The Twenty-Eight Questions" "Novena Of The Twenty-Nine Questions" Chelsea 73 Winter 2002-03, 2004-genm-0923-d-0031; 1 (Box 22)
      - K.C. DUFFiN POEMS CHELSEA, 2004-genm-0923-d-0032; 1 (Box 22)
      - Chelsea 73: Ann Snodgrass ("Two poems" + bio.) title="Lampedusa" 4 pp. (bio. Included) mac/word, 2004-genm-0923-d-0033; 1 (Box 22)
      - Sleepers by Stephanie Kallos, 2004-genm-0923-d-0034; 1 (Box 22)
      - THESE DAYS NOTHING BUT MANIFEST CONTENT FOR DREAMS THE ROAD TO THE ABSOLUTE IS PAVED WITH FLESH SALT SEA OF INVISIBILITIES Michael Tod Edgerton tod@litcity.net, 2004-genm-0923-d-0035; 1 (Box 22)
      - DAVID LUNDE: TRANSLATIONS DuFu: "Written While traveling at Night" "On Yue-yang Tower" Rich Text, 2004-genm-0923-d-0036; 1 (Box 22)
      - Ruth Gila Berger "In-Between", 2004-genm-0923-d-0037; 1 (Box 22)
      - Under the Rainbow BIO Note, 2004-genm-0923-d-0038; 1 (Box 22)
      - GREEN STONES by DOREEN BAINGANA 11-25-02 for CHELSEA, 2004-genm-0923-d-0039; 1 (Box 22)
      - Poems by Dean Kostos (saved on Rich Text Format): "Corot's Red Fleck" "Gate of Ivory" "Gate of Horn", 2004-genm-0923-d-0040; 1 (Box 22)
      - UNREADABLE DISK Daniela Gioseffi 57 Montague St. #8G Brooklyn Hts. New York, NY 11201-3356 2002. Interview with Grace Paley Chelsea Mac Daniela Gioseffi, 2004-genm-0923-d-0041; 1 (Box 22)
      - THE NETTLES by Vénus Khoorz-Ghata, 2004-genm-0923-d-0042; 1 (Box 22)
      - ALBERO with EFFECT July 2000 PHOTO BY VALENTINO VILLA ELABORATA DA ALESSANDRO FABRIZI, 2004-genm-0923-d-0043; 1 (Box 22)
      - KRISTEN CASE "MORNING" "BROOKLYN + THE SEA" "HOUSCIGHTS OF THE VISIBLE WORLD" [WORD FOR P.C.], 2004-genm-0923-d-0044; 1 (Box 22)
      - Chelsea 73 Tim McCarthy RECEIVED MAR 05 2003, 2004-genm-0923-d-0045; 1 (Box 22)
      - REBECCA MEACHAM "Weights + Measures" Mac-formatted disk + stories (also in r.t.f.), 2004-genm-0923-d-0046; 1 (Box 22)
      - [no label information], 2004-genm-0923-d-0047; 1 (Box 22)
      - UNREADABLE DISK UNDER THE RAINBOW BIO. NOTE -Joan Connor, 2004-genm-0923-d-0048; 1 (Box 22)
      - Mike, 2004-genm-0923-d-0049; 1 (Box 22)
      - [no label information], 2004-genm-0923-d-0050; 1 (Box 22)
      - Rosenbaum "Smell of Skunk" saved on Mac in 3 formats, 2004-genm-0923-d-0051; 1 (Box 22)
      - CONNECTIONS: Prose Poems of Rome, Sicily, and Venice by: Emanuel di Pasquale, 2004-genm-0923-d-0052; 1 (Box 22)
      - Six Women Poets TRANS. by di Pasquale AND one women poet trans. by Singh, 2004-genm-0923-d-0053; 1 (Box 22)
      - [no label information], 2004-genm-0923-d-0054; 1 (Box 22)
      - EUGĒNiO DE ANDRADE 6 Poems translated by Alexis Levitin, 2004-genm-0923-d-0055; 1 (Box 22)
      - K. Soniat poems, 2004-genm-0923-d-0056; 1 (Box 22)
      - [no label information], 2004-genm-0923-d-0057; 1 (Box 22)
      - DART Chelsea PAOLO VALESiO trans. G.S., 2004-genm-0923-d-0058; 1 (Box 22)
      - ALBERO PHOTO BY VALENTINO VILLA July 2000, 2004-genm-0923-d-0059; 1 (Box 22)
      - CLARIS WORKS CAN'T READ Chelsea CONTRIBUTORS 73 Macintosh 2 MB MAC FORMAT, 2004-genm-0923-d-0060; 1 (Box 22)
      - Robert Hahn Chelsea Award Poems Micro Soft Word, 2004-genm-0923-d-0061; 1 (Box 22)
      - Shira Dentz WORD FOR MAC, 2004-genm-0923-d-0062; 1 (Box 22)
      - "SOON AND VERY SOON" LARA JK WILSON 47 YALE STREET WINCHESTER, MA 01890 781.721.7691 Lamail@attbi.com, 2004-genm-0923-d-0063; 1 (Box 22)
      - Eliot Khalil Wilson - Poems "Manhattan Afterwards" "Why He left You" saved in Microsoft 5.1 eliotkhalil@excite.com, 2004-genm-0923-d-0064; 1 (Box 22)
      - Burton Raffel "In The Key of G Major" Word for Mac, 2004-genm-0923-d-0065; 1 (Box 22)
      - TOM CARLSON U. of MEMPHIS Rich text version of "WORLD GONE WRONG" Filename: A:ShorethingRichtext.rtf.wpd, 2004-genm-0923-d-0066; 1 (Box 22)
      - MORGAN LUCAS SCHULDT Chelsea Poems Inventing the Body Browsing the Adult Section, 2004-genm-0923-d-0067; 1 (Box 22)
      - Your inept mouth, etc. Brett Alan Sanders translations of prose poems by Maríe Rosa Lojo Rich Text format, 2004-genm-0923-d-0068; 1 (Box 22)
      - SERGE GAVRONSKY WITH HARDLY A TRACE III, VII, XI, XIX, 2004-genm-0923-d-0069; 1 (Box 22)
      - T. Houghton 3 poems for Chelsea 74. 1 Rich text 2 Claris Works from Mac, 2004-genm-0923-d-0070; 1 (Box 22)
      - Aimee Phan "VISITORS", 2004-genm-0923-d-0071; 1 (Box 22)